Peyton Rous Papers 1909-1970 Mss.B.R77
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, ca.1917-1970; 47.0 Linear feet (Box 1-85)
  - Demmon, Emma R
  - Dengler, Henry P
  - Denoix, P F
  - Denstedt, Orville F
  - Denues, A R T
    - Sloan-Kettering Institute for Cancer Research
  - DeOme, K B
  - Detroit Institute for Cancer Research
    - Simpson, William L
  - DeVecchi, Meg
  - Dey, Mrs. John A
  - DeYongh, Crema
  - D'Herelle
    - Claude, Albert
  - Dible
  - Dibner, Bern
  - Dice, Lee Raymond
  - Dick, Macdonald
  - Dickinson, Robert L
  - Dickson, Madeline S
    - Hickson, James J
  - Diehl, Harold S
  - Dieuaide, Francis R
  - Dimmick, Edgar L
  - Dixon, Frank J
  - Doan, Charles A
  - Dobler, H C
  - Dobson, Lindley
  - Dobzhansky, T
  - Dochez, A Raymond
  - Dock, William
  - Dodds, Sir E Charles
  - Doggert, James H
  - Doisy, Ed A
  - Dolan, William D
  - Dole, Vincent P
  - Doljanski, L
    - Halberstaedter, Mrs. Ludwig
  - Dolman, Claude E
    - "Theobald Smith"
  - Donald, Gordon
  - Donner, J W
  - Donner Foundation
    - Schramm, M W S
    - Jamieson, R
  - Donovan, Mary Ellen
  - Dornan, William J
  - Dorr, John V N
  - Douglas, Archibald, Jr.
  - Douglas Gibbons & Co.
  - Downie, A W
    - Dumbell, Keith
  - Dragstedt, Carl A
  - Drane, Hugh, Jr.
  - Draper, George
  - Dravis, Faith
  - Dreier, Hilda J
  - Driessens, J
  - Drinker, Cecil K
    - McMaster, P D
  - Drury, Alan N
  - Drury, Douglas R
  - Duboff, Gregory S
  - DuBois, Eugene F
  - Dubos, Rene J
    - Conner, Lewis A
    - Miller, Phillip
    - Mudd, Stewart
    - Rogers, David
  - Dubose, Mrs. Sarah A
  - DuCret & Co.
  - Duckrey, H
  - Dudziak, Martin J F
  - Duffy, Charles F
  - Duggan, Stephen
  - Dulbecco, Renato
  - Dumbell, Keith
  - Dunbar
  - Dunlop, H E
  - Dunn, Fa-Chi
  - Dunn, John Shaw
  - Dunn, Leslie Clarence
  - Dunn, Mrs. Slava
  - Dunn, Thelma B
  - Dunnington, John H
  - Dunwoody, W N
  - Duran-Reynals, Francisco
    - Beveridge, W I B
    - Shaw, Harry L
    - Cattell, McKeen
    - Oberling, Charles
    - Coggeshall, L T
    - Gardner, W U
    - Ellis, J Marshall
  - DuShane, Graham
  - Duval, Charles W
  - Duve, Christian De
  - Dye
    - Soskin, Samuel
  - Dyer, George
  - Eager, John Howard
  - Eagle, Harry
  - Earls, Francis P
  - Earle, Wilton R
  - Early, J C
  - Easton, John M
    typed 10-3-73
  - Eaton, Monroe D
  - Ebeling, Albert H
  - Eberson, Frederick
  - Ebin, Alexander
  - Echikson, Joseph I
  - Edcan Laboratories
    - Sterling, E C
  - Edel, Leon
  - Edelberg, Benjamin
  - Edelstein, Ludwig
  - Editorials
  - Edmunds, C W
  - Edwards, J Graham
  - Edwards, Joshua
    - McManus, J F A
  - Eggers, H E
  - Eggleston, Margery K
  - Eguiruren, Byron L
  - Ehrlich, Paul, Stiftung
    - Sperl, Friedrich
    - Rothenbuecher, E H
    - Lubke, Heinrich
    - Bernhard, Wilhelm
    - Dulbecco, Renato
    - Curtius, Klaus
    - Strauss, Mrs. E
    - Niessen, Gisela
    - Wittschewsky, Mrs. E
    - Friedrichs, Hanns J
    - Heymann, G
    - Kone, Eugene H
    - Chain, E B
    - Lehmkul, Egon
    - Reinwald, Karl
    - Sormani, Egbert J
    - Mahncke, Horst
    - Biesewig, Gerd
    - Mertens, Josef
    - Schaedel, Willy
  - Ehrich, William
  - Eidinoff, Maxwell L
  - Einstein, Albert, College
    - Gerras, Charles
  - Eisen, Milton J
  - Eisenhower, Milton S
    - Bronk, Detlev W
  - Elliman, Douglas L. & Co.
    - Scott, M L
  - Elliot, Roger Clark
  - Elliot, William J
  - Elliot, Clarence V
  - Elliott, Robert H E., Jr.
  - Ellis, John
  - Elman, Robert
  - Elmore, W C
  - Elsberg, Charles A
    - Mallory, W B
  - Elsmith, Dorothy O
  - Emerson, Haven
  - Emmett, J A
  - Encyclopedia Americana
  - Enders, John F
  - Enders, Robert K
  - Engelbreth-Holm
    - Green, F H K
  - England, Joseph
  - Englander, Mrs. Henry
  - "English Income Tax"
  - Enoki, Yoshisuke
  - Ephrussi, Boris
  - Epstein, M A
  - Erdmann, Rhoda
  - Erickson, Cyrus C
  - Erlanger, Joseph
    - King, M Kenton
  - Estabrook, Arthur H
  - European Tumor Virus Group
    - Bernhard, W
  - Euthanasia Society of America, Inc.
    - Dickinson, Robert L
  - Evans, C J
    - Simpson, Miriam E
  - Evans, Everett Idris
  - Evans, Herbert
    - Simpson, Miriam E
  - Evans, James M
  - Evans, John
  - Ewens, Arthur E
  - Ewing, James
  - Excerpta Medica
    - Woerdeman, M W
    - Cauverien, J
  - Eyges, Mrs. Leonard J
  - Eyster, J A E
  - Faber, Aksel
  - Faber, Harold K
  - Fadiman, Clifton
  - Faeber, E E
  - Faegre, Frances
  - Fahey, Peter R
  - Fahr, Th
    - Hudack, Stephen
  - Failla, G
  - Fardon, John C
  - Farhad, Ahmed
  - Farlow, C., & Co.
  - Farquharson, R F
  - Farr, Lee R
  - Faske-Schirmann
    Typed 10-8-73
  - Faulkner, Mrs. Lizzie Davis
  - Fausold, Eleanor G
  - Fax, Mrs. Reuben
  - Febvre, Henri
    - Assie
    - French Embassy Cultural Division
    - PanAmerican World Airways
    - Crutcher, Miss
    - Oberling, Charles
    - Rivers, Thomas
  - Federal Security Agency
  - Federation of American Scientists
  - Federation of American Societies for Experimental Biology
    - Abel, John J
    - Benedict, S R
    - Blake, Francis G
    - Cullen, Glenn
    - Cushing, Harvey
    - Erlanger, Joseph
    - Hotel Gibson, Cinn., Ohio
    - Schiffeler, C C
    - Henderson, Lawrence J
    - Henderson, Velyien E
    - Henderson, Yandell
    - Hess, Alfred
    - Jackson, D E
    - Lee, Milton O
    - Luckhardt, Arno B
    - MacNider, William DeB
    - Mann, Frank C
    - Mathews, Albert P
    - Meek, Walter J
    - Miller, C Phillip, Jr.
    - Hall, Raymond F
    - Rappleye, Willard C
    - Canby, Robinson
    - Wells, H Gideon
    - Wilson, Russell
    - Hooker, D J
    - McCutcheon, Morton
    - Mattill, H A
    - Chambers, William H
    - Carpenter, Thorne M
    - Leake, Chauncey D
    - Lieb, Charles C
    - Mattill, H A
    - Flinn, Waldo R
    - McFarland, A C
    - Smith, Theobald
    - Barr, D R
    - Gies, William J
    - Bronfenbrenner, J
    - Greene, C W
    - Karsner, Howard T
    - Park, W H
  - Feinberg, Abraham
  - Feldman, William H
  - Fenn, Wallace O
  - Fenner, Frank
  - Ferguson, John
  - Fernandez, Jose M
  - Ferrell, H S
    - Lupinek, Bernard
  - Ferrier Lullin & Cie
  - Ferry, Mansfield
  - Fetter, Theodore R
  - Fewell, A G
  - Field, Madeleine E
  - Fieser, Louis P
  - Fifth International Botanical Congress
    - Rivers, Thomas M
    - Kunkel, L O
    - McKinney, H H
    - Haskell, R J
    - Sherman, J M
  - Fifth International Congress
    - Lacassagne, A
    - Lorier, V Le
  - Filipski, Ronald J
  - Findlay, G M
  - Fine, Jacob
  - Fippinger, Henry
  - First National City Bank of New York
  - Fischer, Albert
  - Fischer, Alfred E
  - Fischer, Fritz
  - Fischler, F
    - Lea & Febiger
    - Lippincott, J.B., Co.
    - Mosby, C.V., Co.
    - Saunders, W.B., Co.
  - Fisher, Irving
    - Fisher, Susan M
  - Fisher, Jack C
  - Fitzgerald, Patrick J
    - Oliver, Jean
  - Flanagan, Curtis J
  - Flath, Carl I
  - Fleming, Donald
  - Fleming, Launcelot
  - Flesch, Peter
  - Fletcher, Norman C
  - Flexner, Abraham
  - Flexner, Mrs. Helen Thomas
    - Kaye, S A
  - Flexner, James Thomas
  - Flexner, M
  - Flexner, Simon, 17 folders
    - Brooks, Mrs. Gladys
      Typed 10-10-73
    - Draper, George
    - Henry, Barklie
    - Jacobs, Walter A
    - Opie, Eugene
    - Sangster, Dorothy
    - Ott, Joan
    - Fishbein, Morris
    - Smith, Edric B
    - Blakeslee, Albert F
    - Clowes, G H A
    - Dakin, Susan & Herbert
    - Graham, Evarts A
    - Henderson, Yardell
    - Kersner, Howard T
    - Parker, G. H.
    - Uhlenhuth, Edward
  - Flexner, Simon. Bibliography
  - Flexner, Simon. Obits.
    - AMA
    - Swift, Homer F
  - Flexner, William W
  - Flinn, Waldo R
  - Florey, Charles
  - Florey, Sir Howard W
  - Florio, Lloyd
  - Flosdorf, Earl W
  - Fluorescent Light Tubes - Warning
  - Flynn, James M
  - Flynn, Joan
  - Flynn, John T
  - Foletar, Joan
  - Foley, Edward J
  - Folkman, Judah
  - Fong, Jacob
  - Foot, N Chandler
  - Foote, Frank W
  - Forbes, E W
  - Forbes, Robert
  - Forbus, Wiley D
  - Forest Park Foundation
    - Rutherford, William L
  - Fortune
    - Wood, Richardson
    - Davenport, Russell W
  - Fosdick, Raymond B
  - Fossi, Nannina
    - Lapi, Luigi
  - Foster, G S
  - Foster, W D
  - Foulds, Leslie
  - Foundation Internationale Balzan
  - Fourfront
  - Fourth International Cancer Research
    - Congress
    - Bayne-Jones, S
    - Kelly, Mrs. Viola
    - Farber, Sidney
    - McGurk, Frank
    - Meader, Ralph G
    - Seelig, M G
    - Warren, Shields
  - Fowler, Kenneth
    - Withane
  - Fox, Herbert
  - Fox, J DeWitt
  - Fox, Robert A
  - Foxe, Anthony M
  - Fraenkel, Marta
    - Muller, Ernst F
  - Francis, Edward
  - Francis Edwards Ltd.
  - Francis, Thomas, Jr.
  - Frankfurter, Felix
  - Franklin, George S
  - Franklin Institute
    - Frazer, John
  - Franks, W R
  - Frazier, W C
  - Free, E E
    - Flexner, Simon
  - French, Fred F., Management Co., Inc.
  - Frenster, John
    - Lyman, Ruth I
  - Freund, Jules
  - Frick, Henry Clay II
  - Fried, Seraphine
  - Friedewald, William F
    - Anderson, Rubert S
    - Kidd, John G
  - Friedheim, Ernst A H
  - Friedlander, Alfred
  - Friedman, Meyer
  - Friend, Charlotte
    - Cambria, Sophie T
  - Frilley, Clotilde
  - Fritsche, Johanna
  - Frost, Folger W
  - Frugoni, Cesare
  - Fruton, Joseph S
  - Fry, C M
  - Fudenberg, Hugh
    - Brainerd, Henry
    - Seldin, Donald W
  - Fudenberg, Mrs. Hugh
  - Fuller Fund
    - Smith, George M
    - Harvey, Samuel
  - Funk, Casimir
    Typed 10-15-73
  - Furnas, J C
  - Furstenberg, A C
  - Furth, Jacob
  - G, J W
  - Gabrielson, Ira N
  - Gage, G E
  - Gajdos, Alfred
  - Gall, Edwin A
  - Gallagher, John E
  - Gallup, Christopher M
  - Gannett, Lewis S
  - Gantt, W Horsley
    - Bush, Alberta E
    - McNee, J W
    - Vaughan, Warren T
  - Gard, Sven
  - Gardner, Raymond E
  - Gardner, William U
  - Garfield, Eugene
  - Garrison, F H
  - Garson, Esther
  - Gasic, Gabriel
  - Gasser, Herbert S, 7 folders
    - Annan, Gertrude
    - Blumenthal, Joseph
    - Cohn, Alfred E
    - Horsfall, Frank L
    - Faerber, E E
    - Fowler, Virginia M
    - Kipper, H B
  - Gastineau, F M
  - Gates, Frederick L
  - Gates, William H
  - Gawthorpe, Mary
  - Gay, Frederick P
    - Jungeblut, Claus W
  - Gaylord, H R
  - Geer, William D
  - Gelatin Capsules
  - General Moving and Storage Co.
  - Gerard, Mrs. R W
  - German, James L
  - Germany, Cultural Attache, New York
  - Germuth, Frederick C., Jr.
  - Gerstell, Richard
  - Gerster, John C A
  - Gerstley, Jesse R
  - Geschickter, Charles F
  - Gesell, Robert
  - Gey, George O
  - Gibbons, Douglas & Co., Inc.
  - Gigon, A
  - Gilbert, A J
  - Gilbert, Judson B
  - Gilbert, Marianne
  - Gilding, Henry P
  - Gillman, Theodore
  - Glaser, Otto
  - Glaser, Rudolf W
  - Gleeten, Scott D
  - Gluck, Elizabeth
  - Goebel, Walther F
  - Goerner, Alfred
  - Gotz, Max
  - Goetz, Robert H
  - Gohlke, Mrs. J Carl
  - Gold Headed Cane
    - Medical Tribune and Medical News
    - Brainin, Joseph
    - Gall, Edward A
    - Whipple, George H
    - Wozencraft, Paul
    - Madden, Sidney
    - Bronk, Detlev W
    - Mezera, Raymond A
    - Kidd, John G
    - Silber, Frederick
  - Goldberger, Mrs. Betty
  - Goldblatt, Harry
  - Goldfedder, Anna
  - Goldforb, A J
  - Goldschmidt, R
  - Goldschmidt, Samuel
  - Goldsmith, M
  - Goldstein, Richard M
  - Goldstone, John L
  - Goldwater, S S
  - Gollob, Stefan
  - Gomez, Robert
  - Goodall, C M
  - Goodner, Kenneth
  - Goodner Memorial Fund
    - Havens, W Paul, Jr.
  - Goodpasture, Ernest
  - Goodson, J C
  - Gordon, Myron
    - Osborn, Fairfield
  - Gorham, L Whittington
  - Gorter, E
    - Flexner, Simon
  - Gosling, Robert
  - Goss, Leonard J
  - Gottesmann, Hilda
  - Gottfried, Mrs. Carolyn Jobst
  - Gottlieb, Robert
  - Gottschalk, Raymond G
  - Gould, H M
  - Gould, Mrs. J H
    Typed 10-16-73
  - Governor Publishing Corporation
    - Sokel, A J
    - Psychology Digest
  - Gowen, John W
    - Claude, A
  - Grace, Edwin J
  - Grace, James D
  - Grady, Hugh G
  - Graef, Irving
  - Graff, Siegfried
  - Graffi, A
  - Graham, Evarts A
  - Graham, George
  - Graham, R W
  - Granda, Gustavo Odio De
  - Granick, Sam
  - Grant, Sandra M
  - Grant, R P
  - Gratia, Andre
  - Graulich, Harry D
  - Gravel Pit-Second Blast
    - Tenney, W Chandler
    - LaBalme, George F., Jr.
    - Cramer, David
    - Calhoun
    - Day, Lee Garnett
    - LaBalme, George
    - Roraback, Catherine G
    - Hoskins, Mrs. Ann
  - Graves, Annie
  - Graves, Stuart
  - Gray, C E
  - Green, Gale R
  - Green, Judith A
  - Green, Myron A
  - Green, Robert
  - Green Mount Cemetery
  - Greene, Elias L
  - Greene, Harry S N
  - Greene, James S
  - Greene, Jerome D
  - Greene, Roger S
  - Greenwald, Isidor
  - Gregg, Alan
    - Lambert, Robert A from Gregg, Alan to Anitschkow, N
  - Gresham, Austin
  - Griffin, John W
  - Griffiths, Cadvan O., Jr.
  - Grimes, Ralph
  - Gross, Ludwik
    - Gasser, Herbert S
    - Warren, A M
  - Grossi, Carlo E
  - Grossman, Sidney
  - Groupe, Vincent
  - Gruen, Sonia L
  - Grundfest, Harry
  - Gudernatch, G S
    - Evarts, Josephine
    - Richards, William R
  - Guerin, Maurice
  - Guggenheim Foundation
    - Moe, Henry Allen
  - Gunn, C K
  - Gustav Stern Symposium
  - Gustus, Edwin L
  - Gutteridge, H C
  - Guttman, Paul H
  - Gutwill, Mrs. Sarah
  - Guyster, Bernard
    - Tamm, Igor
  - Gye, Will E
    - Mueller, J Howard
    - Woglom, William H
    - Archbald, Edward
    - Creegan, Mary Louise
  - Hagen, E
  - Haagensen, Cushman H
  - Hacha
    - Horton, James A
  - Hackel, Donald B
  - Hackett, J C
  - Haddow, Alexander
    - Greenwood, Anne
  - Haessler, F Herbert
  - Hageman, Mrs. Donald
  - Haguenau, Francoise
  - Hairless Mice
    - Cummings, Neville
  - Halasz, Nicholas A
  - Halberstaedter, Mrs. Agnes
  - Halberstaedter, Ludwig
    - Lenz, Maurice
    - Schram, Mildred W S
  - Haldi, John
    - Flexner, Simon
  - Hall, E Raymond
  - Hall of Fame
    - Stein, Mrs. A Harvey
  - Halle, Hiram J
  - Halpern, Bernard
  - Halpern, H
  - Halsted, W H
  - Halvorson, H O
  - Ham, Arthur W
  - Hamburger, Viktor
  - Hamilton, Tonea
  - Hamman, Louis
  - Hammett, Frederick S
    typed 10-18-73
  - Hammond, Mrs. Denis
  - Hamperl, Herwig
  - Hance, Sir James Bennett
  - Hanes, Frederick M
  - Hansen, Jo Ann
  - Hanson, Frank Blair
  - Hansroth, H R
  - Hanzlik, P J
  - Hapgood, Mrs. Norman
  - Harcourt, Brace and Company
    - Salivar, Mildred
  - Harde, Edna
    - Wollstein, Martha
  - Hardin, Robert C
  - Harding, V J
  - Harkavy, J
  - Harkins, Henry N
  - Harmati, Sandor
  - Harper's Magazine
    - Moberg, Verne
  - Harris, Charles C
  - Harris, Geoffroy W
  - Harris, John J
  - Harris, R J C
  - Harris, Roger
  - Harris, Samuel
  - Harris, Stuart
  - Harrison, Ross G
  - Harrison, Mrs. Ellen
  - Harrison, W K
  - Harrop, George A
  - Harsha, William N
  - Hart, Bernard
  - Hart, C Whittlesey
  - Hart, Henry
  - Hart, Mary and Roy
  - Harte, Robert A
  - Hartford, University of
    - Hovey, Daniel
    - Hyndman, Bruce
    - Coffin, Vincent Brown
  - Hartley, Sir Harold
  - Hartline, H D
  - Hartman, Daniel L
  - Hartman, Frank A
  - Hartman, L W
  - Hartwell, John A
  - Harvard University
    - Johnson, John B
  - Harvard University Press
    - Wilson, Thomas J
    - Beldon, Lawrence P
  - Harvey, A McGehee
  - Harvey, Lion
  - Harvey, W F
  - Harvey Lecture
    - Burlingham, Robert
    - Cattell, McKeen
    - Crowell, Marion B
    - Waverly Press, Inc.
    - Williams & Wilkins Co.
    - Palmer, Ola S
    - West, Randolph
    - Palmer, M S
  - Harvey Society
    - Swift, Homer F
    - Rowe, A W
    - Vincent, George E
    - Aub, Joseph C
    - Binger, Carl A L
    - Clark, W Mansfield
    - Grimmel, Grace H
    - Cohn, Edwin J
    - Edwards, Dayton J
    - Carstensen, Grace
    - Flexner, Simon
    - Murphy, James B
    - Herelle, F de
    - Hess, Alfred
    - MacNider, William DeB
    - Opie, Eugene C
    - Palmer, Walter W
    - Leathers, W S
    - Ridley, Evelyn
    - Robinson, G Canby
    - Reynolds, Frederick P
    - Wilson, Louis B
    - Straub, Walther
    - Tenbroeck
    - Vickery, H B
    - Edwards, D J
    - Wallace, George B
    - Mann, Frank C
    - Van Slyke, D D
    - Chambers, Robert
  - Haskell, Helen S
  - Haskins, Mrs. Edna
  - Hass, George M
  - Hastings, Albert Baird
    - Christensen, Halvor N
  - Hatfield, Charles J
  - Havahart Traps
    - Dearman, Mrs. Louise T
    - Conner, Fox B
  - Hawking, Frank
    - Jobling, James W
  - Hawkins, Mrs. Vivian K
  - Haydn, George
  - Hayford, Lawrence D
  - Haythorn, Samuel R
    - Wolbach, Burt
  - Heaney, Norman S
    typed 10-22-73
  - Hedley, W P
  - Heffer, W. and Sons, Ltd.
  - Heggie, R M
  - Heidelberger, Michael
  - Heidelberger, M. Lectureship Fund
  - Heiman, Jacob
  - Heinz Moos Verlagsgesellschaft
  - Hektoen, Ludwig
  - Helburn, Willard
  - Heller, J R
  - Hellfeld, E H
  - Helmer, Oscar M
    - Clowes, G H A
    - Murphy, James B
    - Zerfas, L G
  - Helmholz, Henry F
  - Hemmeter, John C
    - Flexner, Simon
  - Henderson, James Stuart
    - Seitz, Frederick
    - Creech, Hugh J
    - Knutti, Ralph E
    - Leader, R W
    - Orbison, J Lowell
    - Wissler, Robert W
    - Whitaker, Douglas
  - Henderson, Yandell
  - Henderson, L J
  - Hendrick, Burton J
  - Henle, Werner
  - Henrici, Arthur T
  - Henry, Barklie McKee
  - Henry, James
  - Henschen, Folke
  - Henshaw, Paul S
  - Herbertson, Basil Marriott
  - Heretz, Mrs. Alla
  - Herriott, Roger M
  - Herter Lectures
    - Greenwald, Isidor
  - Herzberg, F
  - Herzberg, K
  - Hess, Alfred F
  - Hess, Manfred
    - Dible, J Henry
  - Heston, W E
  - Hestrin, Shlomo
    - Granick, S
  - Heuer, George
    - Carty, John R
  - Hevesy, George De (Mrs. Pia)
    - Molnar, August J
    - Arrhenius, G
    - Putman, J L
    - Wohl, Sonia
    - Seaborg, Glenn T
    - Seligman, Henry
    - Svartz, Nanna
    - Karnofsky, David A
    - Mitchell, Joseph
  - Hewitt, Abraham
  - Hewitt, Abram S
  - Hewitt, Edward R
    - Hewitt, Abram S
  - Hewitt, Harrison
  - Hewitt, Thomas D
  - Hibben, Mrs. Paxton
  - Hicks, John Donald
  - Hieger, I
  - Hien, Albert
  - Hildebrand, E M
  - Hilleman, M R
  - Himwich, Harold E
  - Hinkel, C L
  - Hinkel, Jo
  - Hinsdale, Guy
  - Hinsey, Joseph C
  - Hirsch, James G
  - Hirschfelder, Arthur D
  - Hirst, George K
  - Hirzel, Gertrude
  - Hiss, Alger
  - Hitchcock, David I
  - Hjarre, Albert
  - Hoagland, Charles L
  - Hochman, A
  - Hodes, Robert
  - Hodgkin, Alan
    - Sirtori, Carlo
  - Hodgkin, Mrs. Alan
  - Hodgkin, Dorothy
  - Hodgkin, Keith
  - Hober, Rudolf
  - Hoessly, Grian Fortunat
  - Hofbauer, J
  - Hoffman, Albert
  - Hoffmann, E
    - Rivers, Thomas
  - Hoffnagle, James H
  - Hoffstadt, Rachel E
  - Hogshead, J McChesney
  - Holdridge, Samuel
  - Hollaender, Alexander
  - Holloway, Mary
  - Holman, Russell
  - Holmes, F O
  - Holmes, George F
  - Holmes, Richard
  - Holmes, William F, Jr.
  - Holt, Frank H
  - Holt, Mrs. O T
    typed 10-26-73
  - Holzman, Clara
  - Hon, Conrad
  - Hooker, Charles W
  - Hooker, Donald R
  - Hope-Simpson, R Edgar
  - Hopkins, Joseph Gardner
    - Flexner, Simon
  - Hopkins, Joseph Gardner, Memorial Fund.
  - Hopkins, Samuel
  - Hopps, Howard C
  - Horan, Anthony H
    - Davidson, Charles W
  - Hornstein, George D
  - Horowitz, Samuel B
    - Coggeshall, L T
    - Horsfall, Frank, L, Jr.
  - Horowitz, William
  - Horsfall, Frank L, Jr.
  - Hosek, William
  - Hoskins, Caryl P
  - Hosobuchi, Yoshio
  - Hotels
  - Houghton, Henry S
    - Flexner, Simon
  - Housatonic Valley Regional High School
    - Stoddard, Paul W
  - House of Calvary
    - McParlan, Mrs. Catherine
  - Howard, Campbell P
  - Howard, Frank A
  - Howe, F Stanley
  - Howe, M A DeWolfe
  - Howe, Quincy
  - Howell, William H
    - Hooker, Donald R
  - Howland, Charles P
    - Burlingham, Charles C
  - Hu, C H
    - Pearce, Agnes M
  - Hudack, Stephen S
    - Schurr, Cathleen
  - Hudson, Perry B
  - Huebner, Robert J
  - Hueper, W C
  - Huggins, Charles
    - Talalay, Paul
    - Jensen, Elwood V
    - Canfield, Cass
    - Huxley, Sir Julian
    - Alexander Mrs. Louise
    - Wissler, Robert W
    - Cattell, McKeen
  - Huggins, Charles. Proposals for Nobel and Lasker Awards
    - Lasker, Mrs. Albert D
    - Li, Choh Hao
    - Ingle, Dwight J
  - Hunt, Bertha
  - Hunt, George
  - Hunter, Oscar B, Jr.
  - Hunter, Tom
  - Huntington, Mrs. Anna Hyatt
    - Campbell, Charles I
  - Huntley, Victoria
    - Moe, Henry Allen
  - Hurst, E Weston
    - Shope, Richard E
  - Huseby, Robert A
    - Boring, M Frances
    - Schram, M W S
  - Hussey, Raymond
  - Husted, Jean
  - Hutchins, Robert M
  - Huxley, Sir Julian
  - Hyde, Roscoe R
  - Hyman, Harold T
  - Hyman, O W
  - Ibarra, Ramon
  - Icebox
  - Idoine, Leon S
    - Crutcher, K G
  - Iglesias, Rigoberto
  - Illustration Service Requisition
    (Rockefeller Institute)
  - Imboden, H M
  - Imperial Cancer Research Fund
    - Marrian, G F
    - Ingle, Dwight J
    - Wakeley, Sir Cecil
    - Harris, R J C
    - Clarke, A B L
    - Henderson J Stuart
    - Bacon, Margaret
  - Income Tax - New York
  - Index Biologicorum
  - Indicators
    - Richards, A N
    - Edwards, J Graham
    - Cohen, Barnett
  - Industria Ceramice Avallone
  - Ingalls, Mabel S
  - Ingle, Dwight J
  - Ingvolstad, Mrs. Carl
    - Compton, Arthur H
  - Institute for Mediterranean Affairs
    typed 10-30-73
    - Albright, William F
  - Institute for Propaganda Analysis
  - Institute - Pending
    - McMaster, Philip D
  - Instituto Cajal
    - Lambert, R A
    - Robertson, Albert D
    - Peck, M B
  - Insurance
  - Internal Revenue - U.S.
  - International Alpine University
  - The International Association of Medical Museums
  - International Congress of Scientific and Social Campaign against cancer, II see:
    - Brussels. Belgian
    - National League Against cancer
  - International (XIX) Physiological Congress
    - Selye, Hans
  - International Who's Who
  - Interurban Clinical Club
    - Stewart, Harold J
  - Invitations
  - Iongh, D Crena De
  - Irish, Miss Lurene
  - Isaacs, Alick
  - Ito, Yohei
    - Fujinami, Mrs.
  - Iversen, Olav Hilmar
  - Ivins, William M, Jr.
  - Ivy, A C
  - Jackson, C M
  - Jackson, Dudley
  - Jackson Memorial Lab
    - Flynn, T E
    - Little, C C
    - Keucher, Elizabeth
    - Sawin, Paul B
    - Snell, George D
    - Fekete, Elizabeth
    - Cloudman, Arthur M
    - Woolley, George W
    - Snell, George D
    - Keucher, Elizabeth
    - Strong, L C
    - Bittner, John J
    - Harris, Donald
    - Anthony, J F
  - Jacobs, M H
  - Jacobs, W A
  - Jacobson, Julius II
  - Jacod, Louis F. & Co.
  - Jaffe, Henry L
  - Jaffin, Henry
  - James
  - James, Mrs. Dorothea
  - James, Edward T
  - James, Henry
    - Edel, Leon
    - Gasser, H S
    - Greene, Jerome D
  - James, T L
  - Jarcho, Mrs. Jeanette
  - The Jefferson Medical College and Medical Center
  - Jelliffe, Smith Ely
  - Jenkins, Morris S
  - Jennings, Sir Ivor
  - Jennings, W M
  - Jernberg, Nils
  - Jerome, Fred N
  - Jobling, James W
  - Johns Hopkins University
    - Abercrombie, Ronald T
    - Edmunds, C K
    - Trumbull, Bayard
    - Paullin, James E
    - Brady, James H., Jr.
    - Mullin, J Morfit
  - Johns Hopkins University. Alumni Association
    - Richardson, Edward H
    - Abercrombie, Ronald T
    - Vanderhoof, Douglas
  - The Johns Hopkins University. Class of 1900
  - Johns Hopkins University School of Medicine
    - Moss, W L
    - Talalay, Paul
    - Eisenhower, Milton S
    - Turner, Thomas B
    - Clark, W Mansfield
    - Paullin, James E
  - Johnson, Mr. & Mrs.
  - Johnson, Earl
    - Shope, Richard E
  - Johnson, Harald N
  - Johnson, Lloyd
  - Johnson, Marvin O
    - Flexner, Simon
  - Johnson, R. W.
  - Johnson, Walter J., Inc.
  - Johnston, Mrs. Kent
  - Johnston, M D
  - Jones, Beatrice Pinkney
  - Jones, Donald F
  - Jones, Frederick D
  - Jones, Frederick Snowden
    typed 11-9-73
    - Smith, Theobald